https://www.lafayetteindustries.com/lafayette-privacy-policy/

MENUMENUHome
Lafayette Latest NewsGuardian/Consumer PortalDonateGet Involved
About
History & MissionBoard of DirectorsAnnual ReportStaff DirectoryVolunteer and InternshipsLafayette Privacy Policy
Contract Packaging
Packaging
Flow WrappingBlister PackagingCartoning GluingClam Shell PackagingCoding and LabelingDisplay AssemblyShrink Wrapping
AssemblyMedical PackagingMailing and FulfillmentLogistics and WarehousePackaging NewsRequest a Quote
STEPUP
Keeping on, keeping connected!Schedule Interview & TourStaff EmploymentFAQ
Contact Us
Map & Directions
Lafayette Website Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.lafayetteindustries.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
How policy changes will be communicated.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
name, address, email address, credit card information
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to get more information to fulfill your request.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Changes to this Policy
We may make changes to this privacy notice from time to time. You may check back on this page at any time to see our current policy.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 636-227-5666 or sales@lafayetteindustries.com.
179 Gaywood DriveManchester, MO 63021636-227-5666
Employee Portal
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Facebook
Twitter
Linkedin
Copyright 2020 Lafayette Industries. All Rights Reserved.
Copyright © 2019-present Lafayette Industries.
All Rights Reserved.
Close Menu
